Going back to the wire frames. In the phone layout, we
wanted the today item to be a little bit bigger. But on
the tablets, we just want it to look like all the
other items, because we have an expanded detail pane here. To do
this in the forecast adapter new view method, we should return
the layout for a list item forecast not for the today layout.
Then in the bind view method, for the today item, we
should use the gray icon instead of the colored icon. These decisions
get controlled by the return value of the getItemViewType method. Therefore,
we modify the getItemViewType method so that at the zero position,
if we have to use the special today layout, then we
return view type today. Otherwise, if we shouldn't use the special
today layout, then we should just return the view type for
all future days. This Boolean is controlled by the setter method.
To access this Boolean, we created a public setter method on
the forecast adapter. But who knows how to set this value properly?
Well the main activity knows whether it's one pane,
or two pane UI. So, it can decide whether
we should use the special today layout or not.
We don't have access to the forecast adapter here, but
we can plumb the value through the forecast fragment.
To get access to the forecast fragment, we can ask
the fragment manager and pass it the fragment ID.
Finish changing the code so the app looks like this.